Guide to the George B. Dantzig Papers
Stanford University Libraries.
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2005-363
  - Transporation Problem- Miscellaneous Notes, February 1949 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Prog. of Interdependent Activities IT- Math. Model, May 1949 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Application of Simplex Method to Hithcock-Koopmans Transportation Problem, February 1949 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Progress reports, 1953-1960 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Computation of Char. Root and Eigen-Vector of Positive Matrix, 10/28/1952 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Computing Eigen-Vector by Running Substitution, 11/6/1952 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Notes on Bellman Process Selection Problems, 11/12/1952 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Examples of Models, 12/8/1952 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Symmetric Air War (Rought Notes), August 1951 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Optium Personnel Policty for Hiring, 12/14/1950 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Leontif Dynamic System - Continuous Models, Winter 1950 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Duality Theorum Baswed on Simplex 21 Method (Symposium on Linear Inequality and Programming), 6/14/1951 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Solving Equations by Simplex Technique, 7/18/1951 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Letter to A. Tucker on Non-Covex Programming, July 1951 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Computation of Max-Effort Minimum Force Probems, 8/1/1951 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Peace-War Expansion Procedure, 8/14/1951 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Abstract Minneapolis Meeting, 9/4/1951 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Comments on Seton's MS on Properties of Leontief Matrices, October 1951 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Chart fofr Determining A/C Production Requirements, 10/3/1951 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - DRAFT: Air Force Manual for Application of Linear Programming Techniques, 10/5/1951 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Introduction to Air Force Manual on LInear Prog. Tech., 10/5/1951 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - DRAFT: Air Force Manual for Application of Linear Programming Techniques, 10/5/1951 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Expansion Limitation Procedure, 10/19/1951 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Notes on Linear Spaces and Vector Space, 12/5/1951 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Files of Unsolved Linear Prog. Prob. and New Problem Areas Special Exercises, 12/7/1951 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Estimating IMprovement in Random 46 Gradient Method, 12/13/1951 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Comments on Marlow's Paper beforeGWU Logistics Symposium, January 1952 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Notes on Duality, 1/28/1952 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Memo for Colonel B.J. Webster Recommendation on SCOOP, 1/291952 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Solving Interindustry Matrix, 12/13/1951 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Leontief Substituitoin Convergence of Rate (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Reference System, 2/7/1952 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - A Note on a Dynamic Leontrif Model Substitution, 2/12/1952 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Simplex Solution fo rthe Dynamic Linear Programming Problem, 12/13/1952 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Bibliography George Dantzig (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - A Note on Charnes' Paper on Optimality, 5/20/1952 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Comments on JV Neumann's - The Prob. of Assign. in a Two-Person Game, 7/20/1952 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Review by GBD for Scripts Mathematics - Contributions to Theory of Games, 9/25/1952 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Talk before Production Programming Seminar, September 1952 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Notes on a Bellman Control Problem, 1024/1952 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Honors and Invitations (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - GBD's Personal Calendars, 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - George B. Dantzig: Letters and memos, 1953-1955 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Algebraic Proof of Min Max Theorem, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Linear Model of Production, 10/21/1952 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Dynamic Scheduling of Ships, March 1953 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller (USAF) Simplex Code, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Application of L.P. to AIF Problems, 12/17/1954 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Corresp. on Job Opportunities Outside USAF, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Andy Marshall Stockpile Problem, 12/8/1952 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Algorithm for COmputing Optimum Distribution of Local Defense - RM 914, 8/12/1952 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Simplex Solution to a Trasportation Problem of the (I,J,K) Type, 9/10/1952 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Talk on Linear Programming, June 23 1953, Aug 18 1953 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence File, 1952-1956 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Jan to June), 1953 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Barankin, Edward W., 1948 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Institute Numerical Analysis, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (USAF), 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Letters to Laderman Simplex Algorithm, Dec 1947/Sept. 1947 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Wallis, Allen, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - First Simplex Method Computations, Summer 1947 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - AMC SCOOP Supply Procedure, October 1947 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Outline of Talk Given BLS (Cornfield), 6/26/1947 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Various Meetings, Talks Given, Correspondence Thereto, 1949-1952 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence April - June, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence July - September, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence October - December, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence January - March, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence File, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - A, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - E, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - F, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - G, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - H, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - I, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - J, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - K, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - L, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - M, Jan-May 1960 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Final Exam OR 373, Fall 1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Renewal Proposal for Research in Mathematical Programming Language, 10/25/1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Mathematical Programming Language - Users Guide, June 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration from Duke University, December 1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Some Comments on Computer Languages for Mathematical Programming Problems, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Mathematical Programming Language Specification Manual for Committee Review, November 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Term Paper: IE 290D by Saul I Gass, 1/28/1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Various Papers on the Mathematial Programming Language, 1967-1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Gibbs Lecture - The Wide Wide / Also Hunter - Influence of Decision Sci., undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Work Assignments for Energy, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - PILOT Projects, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Personal Calendar, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Reminiscences, circa 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Planning Under Uncertainty Talk, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Parallel Processors Text, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - ONR - SOL: Proposal, February 1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Freshman Seminar, 4/12/1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - OR 389 - Conditioned Limit Theorems, Winter 1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Seminars - Computer Revolution and Environmental Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Problems (Exam Questions), March 1969 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - WM Drews - GBD Top Left File, June 1977 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - F86 Study Section Materials, Spring 1956 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Oral Exam Questions, 3/13/1969 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Federal Energy Administration, February 1976 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - I.E. 262, Jan 1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - EPRI/ERDA Proposals, November 1976-October 1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Stanford's Institue for Energy Studies, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Chapter 4 - Linear Equation and Inequality Systems, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Various letters and proposals, 1977, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Various Lectures on Generalized Functions, Errata and Linear Programming, 1955, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Linear Programming Methods, July 1948 (Box 13.1, Folder 1)
  - Controller HQ, USAF, 17817 (Box 13.1, Folder 2)
  - Headquarter U.S. Airforce Controller, 17931 (Box 13.1, Folder 3)
  - Application of the Simplex Method to a Game Theory Problem, 18055 (Box 13.1, Folder 4)
  - USAF Controller, 18057 (Box 13.1, Folder 5)
  - Controller USAF, 18069 (Box 13.1, Folder 6)
  - GBD & BCE: Fourier-Motzkin Elimination and its Dual, November 1972 (Box 13.1, Folder 7)
  - GBD: The ORSA New Orleans Address on Compact City (TIMS), 26603 (Box 13.1, Folder 8)
  - Application of Decomposition to Transportation Network Analysis, March 1976 (Box 13.1, Folder 9)
  - Application of Decomposition to Transportation Network Analysis, December 1975 (Box 13.1, Folder 10)
  - MAA Studies No. 11 (Fulkerson, editor), 1973-1975 (Box 13.1, Folder 11)
  - Generalized Upper-Bound (Original), 1966-1968 (Box 13.1, Folder 12)
  - GBD: Research Problem, 26570 (Box 13.1, Folder 13)
  - GBD: "The Story of the Simplex Method", n/a (Box 13.1, Folder 14)
  - Linear Programming - Charnes Symposium, 1977, 1978 (Box 13.1, Folder 15)
  - The Stanford PILOT Energy/Economic Model, July 1977 (Box 13.1, Folder 16)
  - "Deriving a Utility Function for the U.S. Economy", 1989 (Box 13.1, Folder 17)
  - Compensitory Harmonic Motion in Cerebral Palsy, 1973 (Box 13.1, Folder 18)
  - Draft/GBD-TR, 26820 (Box 13.1, Folder 19)
  - Prize Documents, 1 set, 32140 (Box 13.1, Folder 20)
  - F. Dantzig, G.B. (Bio-Bibliography Data) Folder No.2, 1964 (Box 13.1, Folder 21)
  - Mathematical Programming Language MPL/C Reference Manual by Thomas S. Hedges, August 1975 (Box 13.1, Folder 22)
  - Researched Proposals- PILOT Model for Assessing Energy-Economic Options, July 1976, May 1977 (Box 13.1, Folder 23)
  - Linear Programming Problems, n/a (Box 13.1, Folder 24)
  - Notes on Linear Programming: Part XV - Minimizing the Number of Carriers to Meet a Fixed Schedule, 34 August 1954 (Box 13.1, Folder 25)
  - New Directions in Mathematical Programming and A Proposed Implementation of Compact City, 1959, 1975 (Box 13.1, Folder 26)
  - A Model Airforce and Programming in a Linear Structure, circa 1948 (Box 13.1, Folder 27)
  - Prospectus for the AAF Electronics prog. comp., June 1946 (Box 13.1, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Papers to Sort, n/a (Box 13.1, Folder 29)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1990-1992 (Box 13.1, Folder 30)
  - Loose Items to Sort, Spring 1994 (Box 13.1, Folder 31)
  - Gould & Garcia, 1990 (Box 13.1, Folder 32)
  - Loose Items to Sort (OR 342), Spring 1994 (Box 13.1, Folder 33)
  - Complex Variables (Lecture Notes for AMa95a - P.G. Saffman, n/a (Box 13.1, Folder 34)
  - Loose Items to Sort (CS 237), 1994 (Box 13.1, Folder 35)
  - Prize Documents, Muster, 12/88 (Box 13.1, Folder 36)
  - Prize: (Info for RWC), 11/82 (Box 13.1, Folder 37)
  - Loose Items to Sort, n/a (Box 13.1, Folder 38)
  - Loose Items to Sort, n/a (Box 13.1, Folder 39)
  - Assorted Notes and Code on Linear Programming, n/a (Box 13.1, Folder 40)
  - Mathematical Programming Under Uncertainty for Portfolio Optimization, August 1990 (Box 13.2, Folder 1)
  - Various Papers by Hiroshi Konno, 1989 (Box 13.2, Folder 2)
  - Various Papers on Decision Theory/Analysis, 1988-1991 (Box 13.2, Folder 3)
  - Proceedings of the Workshop on Resource Planning Under Uncertainty - Stanford University, January 21-22, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Members Register - Israel Institute of Technology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Bulletins, 200-2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Compact City by George Dantzig and Thomas L. Saaty, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Member Comments - National Academy of Engineering, February 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Letter and Paper from Bruce Shepherd, 36753 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Letter and Paper from William Cooper, 36917 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Memoirs - George Dantzig, January 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Australia MS: Reminiscences, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Linear Programming and its Progeny (Technical File), n/a (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Assorted Printed Articles, n/a (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Early Rand: Personalities and Projects as Recalled in the Alumni Bulletin by James Digby, March 2001 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Various Papers from the Israel Institute of Technology, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Letter and Paper from the RAND Alumni Association, April 2001 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - The Allocation of Aircraft to Routes - An Example of Linear Programming Under Uncertain Demand, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Various Problems and Papers by George Dantzig, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - ORMS Today Magazines, October 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 85th Birthday Celebration Programs, November 1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - The DIA Equity Portfolio Optimizer System, August 1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Honorary Doctorate from the University of Cyprus - Letters, 36830 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Tel Aviv University Research Catalog, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Various papers, articles, circa 2000 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Risk Constrained Optimization vs. Extremization by Dr. Masch, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Math Programming Information (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - ORMS Today Magazines, December 1999 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2006-167
  - Gomory Intgegr Prog. Notes (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Helmer Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hospital Admissions - Health Antibiotic Model (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Triangularized Basis Inverse (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Updating the product form of the inverse for the revised simplex method" (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Israel Technical Discussions (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Koopman-Manne Program: Complementary Problem (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - KUHN (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lagrange (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Richard Sasaki (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Learning Problem Notes (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Maximum Payload Network Flow, Dr. Johnson & G.B. Dantzig (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Medical Diagnosis (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Mediterranean Dead Sea Power System (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Formulation of Milk Dist Model Carnation (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Min Arc Cover (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Models Sugar (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Large Scale Optimization" (Decomposition Comf) - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Matroids - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Q.R. In the World of Today and Tomorrow" - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Educational Models Yoon-Gee Min (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Natural Gas Discussions with Van Slyke (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Network Flow Notes - Oliver I.E. 266 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "New Mathematical Methods in the Life Sciences" - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Nonlinear Prof. Notes (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "On the Continutiy of the minimum set of a continous function" - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "On the significance of solving Integer Programming" (Tahoe Talk) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Optimal Asisignment of Computer Storage by Chain Decomposition of Partially Ordered Sets" - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Patients (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Permanent Conjecture (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Positive Matrices (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - On V Principal Minors Positive (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Ratinoal Approximation (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - "Discussion on Pricing" (Dorfman-Dantzig) - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Simple Pivot Rules GBD (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Tchebycheff's Problem (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Pivot Rules for the Simplex Method - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Quadratic Programming (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Zassenhaus (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "The School Scheduling Problem" - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sigmap (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Research in Progress (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - "On Steady-State Interncompartmental Flow" join w/Levin, Bigelow (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Steepest Ascent - Cottle (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - "Symmetrioc Dual Nonlinear Programs" - Technical File (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Travelling Salesman (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Integer Programming (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - "Uncertainty" - Thechnical File (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Deriving Utility (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Linear Programming and Extensions Folder 5, 1963 Sep (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Deriving a Utility Function for the Economy (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - GBD Pilot (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Beale Symposium Pilot/Utility? (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Econ Growth and Dynamic Growth (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Economy Objective Paper (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Using Pilot to Assess Impact of a New Tech on Society IBM-Almbaden, 1986 Sep 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Deriving/Formulating an Objective for the Economy (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Uncertainty Tack (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wide-Wide-World of Pure Math (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Von Neumann Algorithm Papers (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - A Build-Up Interior method for Linear Programming - George B. Dantzig and Yinyu Ye (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Untitled (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Uncertainty (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Untitled (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Uncertainty (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Utlity Function/Tech Assess (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Equilibrium (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Marcfh 11-12. 1988: Shoven, Equilibrium Workshop, NBER (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - A Build-Up Interior Method for Linear Programming - Yinyu Ye (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Analyzing Effects of Technological Change (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Analyzing the Effects of Technological Change a Computable Equlibrium Approach (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - A Theorum on Linear Inequalities Referred to by von Neumann (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Untitled (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Discussions with Leonid Hurwitz (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Prospectus for AAF Elecotronical Program Computer, 1947 Jun (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - A Procedure for Max Linear Form Program in a Linear Structure (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - SCOOP, 10/12/1948 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Prospectus for an A/F Mathematical Computation Cneter, 6/29/1948 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Use of Electronical Computers in MilAirStaff Briefing on "Scientific Planning, Tech. SCOOP No. 1", 8/5/1948 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondance 1953 (July to Dec) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondance 1954 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Correspondance 1955 (Jan through June) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Correspondance 1955 (July throught December) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Correspondance, January-March, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Untitled (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Names and Addresses of Students (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - F. Dantzig, George B. (Misc Personal Correspondance), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Early Computations Instructions (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Leak of Early Papers on LP (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Commendations (Early) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondance (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Early Degeneracy Papers (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stochastic Programming Reference List (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Prints of Photos - Final Form extras (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Compact City - GBD's Copy of Drawings (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Untitled (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Book (new) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Compact City: Transparencies + Master (Old trans. from frames) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Old Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - CC Transparencies (New?) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Compact City: Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Compact City Slides (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - President's Correspondance. Ralph "Jim" Reynolds Incoming N, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ASSU Senate Agenda, 3/1/1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ASSU Senate Agenda, 4/5/1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sol Softward Correspondance OLD (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Transparencies for Class Preparation (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Transparencies (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Untitled, Spring 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 186 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - President's Correspondence: Ralph "Jim" Reynolds Incoming O-R, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - President's Correspondence: Incoming A-E, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - President's Correspondence: Ralph "Jim" Reynolds Incoming Incoming F-M (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Presiden'ts Correspondence: Wallace S. Brooke Incoming A-H, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - President's Correspondence: Wallace S. Brooke Incoming T-R, 1935-1936 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Presiden'ts Correspondence: Wallace S. Brooke Incoming, 1932-1935 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Feasibility Study for Future City (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Compact City (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Future (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Proposals File, 1993-96 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Technion-Israel Technology (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Proposal 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Notes (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hojati Mehran, Autumn 1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - FAA Free Flight Proposal (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Teaching Evaluations (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - DR Propoganda (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Invitations (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Job Opportunities (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Vitae (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Exam Questions (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Memoirs (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Course Descriptions (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Book Contracts (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Lists (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - EPRI (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - DOE (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - EPRI (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - NSF (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Annual Faculty Report (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Unrestricted Funds (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Administrative (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - AMS SF Meeting - The Wide World of Pure math, 1/9/1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Reminscence or Letters (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Memoirs about my own Contributions to Linear Programming and Extnesions by GB Dantzig (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - ASSU Senate Agenda, 3/3/1987 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - GBD Biographical (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Memories, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Memoirs (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Linear and Nonlinear programming game theory (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - ASSU Senate Agenda, 2/24/1987 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Dantzig's Program for PHD Final Exam (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Reprintic (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - The WIde World of Math that Goes By Other Names (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Rees ms Fernbach (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Misc. Corresp. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Solving Large-Scale L.P.S., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Large Scale Continuous Examples (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Large Scale Survey Lecture (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Large Scale Staircase (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Large Scale Notes (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Sol. Research Big Picture, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - (Not Labeled) Expected Number of Steps of the Simplex Method - Technical Report, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Barrier Notes/ Sol. Exp. for Solving L.P.S. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Experiments, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Transparencies: Transportation Talk ORSA, 4/1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Concerns About Large-Scale Models TEXT, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Tiling, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Decomposition Principle Eliminating Unwanted Variables (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - "Operational Sciences" What should be the nature of its support by NSF (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Talk-Making Progress During a Stall, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Handout #10, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - SU/UCB Colloquium, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Random Thoughts about Complexity, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Forum Reading Material, 10/1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Energy Technical Reports, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Correspondence, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Exhibits, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - PILOT, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Solutions, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - PILOT Financial Model, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - PILOT Project List, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Wollmer, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Energy Technical Reports, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Energy Inst. SOL Reports, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Computation Algorithm of Simplex Method by George B. Dantzig, 4/1953 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Freshman Energy Seminar, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Energy Memo Packet, 6/1976 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Examination Questions, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exam Questions, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - (Not Labeled) Lecture XII: Duality Theorems, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - OR340A Exams Test Prob. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - (Not Labeled) Various Problems (Box 7, Folder 5)